<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yuchen Niu</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Yuchen Niu</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hue3a655598c6865a5273e9cfb01f02a1f_2400_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Yuchen Niu</title>
      <link>https://example.com/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Generalization Ability of Pretrained Language Models on Arithmetic and Logical Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://example.com/publication/plm_arithmetic_logic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/publication/plm_arithmetic_logic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- &lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click the &lt;em&gt;Cite&lt;/em&gt; button above to demo the feature to enable visitors to import publication metadata into their reference management software.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Create your slides in Markdown - click the &lt;em&gt;Slides&lt;/em&gt; button to check out the example.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


Supplementary notes can be added here, including [code, math, and images](https://wowchemy.com/docs/writing-markdown-latex/). --&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Performance Characterization of Serverless Computing</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/ug_thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/ug_thesis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Serverless computing is a growing cloud framework that removes the barriers of resource provision and scaling from the cloud users. Function-as-a-Service (FaaS) is a
way to deploy an application, as a set of functions, to serverless backends in the cloud.
The functions are usually short-lived and have unpredictable invocation patterns. A
typical cloud environment has multiple tenants coreside on a server. The combination
of the multitenancy and functions’ characterization leads to that a serverless platform
has to address the potential overheads of burstable invocations. This project studies the
architectural implications of serverless computing under a high multitenancy. We explicitly measure the throughput and hardware performance counters of a server while
the number of tenants varies. We find that the server suffers an approximately 40%
of throughput loss when the number of tenants exceeds the number of physical cores.
The characteristics of hardware performance counters show that the contention of data
demands on the memory subsystem is rapidly aggravated as the number of tenants increases. When two tenants coreside on the same physical core, the contention on the
instruction fetch may overtake the stalls in the memory subsystem. We also conform
that the interleaves short functions from multiple tenants are harmful to the localitypreserving microarchitectural structures. We open-source an automated profiling tool
in the vHive, which we developed for this project.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Practical</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/mlp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/mlp/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>System Design Project</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/sdp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/sdp/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Informatics Large Practical</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/ilp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/ilp/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/admin/config.yml</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/admin/config.yml</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
